If you want to review data, you need to be in the "Review" tab.
Here you will find the three different statuses "Needs review",
"Rejected" and "Accepted".
As soon as a data package has been submitted for review by a data provider,
it will be displayed under "Needs review".
When you select a package, you will see all its contents on the right side.
To view the metadata, use the book icon.
You will find it at different levels of the package.
Each file can have metadata, each folder
or the whole package can have metadata.
If you open the metadata form by using the book symbol,
you can check the metadata entered by the data provider.
To ensure the completeness of the legal entries,
use the list icon displayed next to the data package.
You can check the data provider´s entries under the "Legal" tab.
You can also use the list icon to give the data provider feedback on their data.
Choose the "Review" tab and you can enter your feedback in the "New Comment" field
and use the "Add to review" button.
If necessary, you can also delete the current review using the recycle bin.
To make your reviews visible to the data provider in the next step,
you need to reject the data package for revision.
To do this, use the "Request changes" button at the bottom.
The status of the data package will now change from "Needs review" to "Rejected".
As soon as the package has been processed by the data provider,
it will reappear with the status "Needs review".
It can then either be sent back to the data provider
with new reviews for processing again,
or the data package can be archived without further complaint.
To do this, use the "Accept & Archive" button in the top right.
The data package will now change to the status "Accepted"
and will also appear as "Archived" to the data provider.